<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
  <author>Zasz</author>
  <title>Home PC v3.0</title>
  <description />
  <content>&lt;div&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Check it out @ &amp;nbsp;&lt;span class="Apple-style-span" style="font-family: 'lucida grande', tahoma, verdana, arial, sans-serif; color: #333333"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.facebook.com/album.php?aid=281802&amp;amp;id=815596121&amp;amp;l=cb4a23b17f"&gt;Facebook Images&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;- &amp;nbsp;There are a few neat things I can share here :&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Power Supply required for your custom configuration can be calculated here :&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="http://www.antec.outervision.com/"&gt;http://www.antec.outervision.com/&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;It helps you make decision on the proper PSU/SMPS for your machine. Mine is around 345 Watts - so I got a 400W Zebronics SMPS (take into account ageing and surges)&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Most monitors are LCD which means they have a white backlight source burning all the time behind and any blackness and colors are rendered by shining it through liquid crystals turned by electricity. Which means black is not really black but is sort of bright gray, and power is wasted by throwing light and blocking it. My LED monitor works by radiating appropriate color light, and not burning at all in black regions on the screen. &amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;LED is mostly seen in TVs and they cost 30k and above for even being HD-Ready [720p max supported resolution]&amp;nbsp;26 inches, and full HD [1080p] are available only for 32 inches and above, this acer monitor I bought is 24 inches AND LED technology AND Full HD AND only 15K - almost too suspicious to be true, but its bought Ill follow up here if it screws up.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;For a decent Gaming and Dev PC, &amp;nbsp;Core i5 7XX (4 Core) is the best :&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;No matter what Intel says - Core i7 gives only a very small improvement over i5 and only in Physics heavy games (Think shooters and a few RTS titles) and the physics rendered by those engines is usually on collisions and explosions and on Faces only which are themselves grainy to start with and last only for half a second or so.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.geek.com/articles/games/nvidia-proves-intels-core-i7-is-money-wasted-for-gamers-20090430/"&gt;http://www.geek.com/articles/games/nvidia-proves-intels-core-i7-is-money-wasted-for-gamers-20090430/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.geek.com/articles/games/nvidia-proves-intels-core-i7-is-money-wasted-for-gamers-20090430/"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.bit-tech.net/news/hardware/2009/04/23/core-i7-waste-of-money-says-nvidia/1"&gt;http://www.bit-tech.net/news/hardware/2009/04/23/core-i7-waste-of-money-says-nvidia/1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Clock speed increase is only 210 MHz, and Cache size is same, HT tech is enabled for i7 not for 4-core i5. &amp;nbsp;I am talking about Core i5 7XX series here which are quad core with 4 concurrent threads no HT - not the Core i5 4XX, 5XX and 6XX series which have only 2 core and still manage 4 threads by using HT. Prefer 2 extra cores over HT. Only core i7 gives both 4 cores and HT enabling 8 concurrent threads.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;On a side note :&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Home PC v0.0 was P3 550 MHz, 64 MB Ram, Integrated Graphics.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Home PC v1.0 was P4 2.8 GHz, 256 MB Ram, nVidia 5400 256 VRAM.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Home PC v2.0 was P4 3.0 GHz, 1 GB Ram, ATI HD 4650 512 MB VRAM (PC World Best buy in 2007).&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.bit-tech.net/news/hardware/2009/04/23/core-i7-waste-of-money-says-nvidia/1"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;</content>
  <ispublished>True</ispublished>
  <iscommentsenabled>True</iscommentsenabled>
  <pubDate>2011-01-07 08:33:00</pubDate>
  <lastModified>2011-01-07 08:59:32</lastModified>
  <raters>1</raters>
  <rating>5</rating>
  <slug>Home-PC-v30</slug>
  <tags>
    <tag>games</tag>
  </tags>
  <comments>
    <comment id="f620ebba-cd10-4ea3-b1ad-569da8fd0a04" approved="True">
      <date>2011-01-10 03:46:27</date>
      <author>pea coats for women</author>
      <email>hang@126.com</email>
      <ip>61.190.27.42</ip>
      <website>http://www.sfyh.com/pea-coats-for-women_ss</website>
      <content>I really appreciate the effort you have given to this post. I am looking forward for your next post. I found this informative and interesting blog. I just hope you could make another post related to this. This is definitely worth reading.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="cb8bea11-bbff-4b59-a3f4-326bd45ba629" approved="True">
      <date>2011-01-16 05:47:40</date>
      <author>Tony</author>
      <email>desinghrajan@ymail.com</email>
      <ip>117.199.130.69</ip>
      <content>Good Job Soldier...</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="0e4c2523-e6b9-4a91-8604-bd89fdbb7a5f" approved="True">
      <date>2011-01-27 06:24:40</date>
      <author>knee high leather boots</author>
      <email>hang@126.com</email>
      <ip>61.190.27.42</ip>
      <website>http://www.sfyh.com/knee-high-leather-boots_ss</website>
      <content>hey! i love shakeitphoto! with this update, you can use existing photos you already have... you can also process this photo again and again for a really cool look!</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="981f5651-0a52-467b-9515-f7c8f1143ab5" approved="True">
      <date>2011-02-15 06:08:51</date>
      <author>bass acoustic guitars</author>
      <email>hang@126.com</email>
      <ip>216.83.63.50</ip>
      <website>http://www.sfyh.com/bass-acoustic-guitars_ss</website>
      <content>Wow nice info you have here. I wish this will help a lot of people. I will tell my friends to read this. Thanks!</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="f5565c40-9598-49c3-9b4e-783f687101c7" approved="True">
      <date>2011-02-17 08:49:10</date>
      <author>totes snow boots</author>
      <email>hang@126.com</email>
      <ip>216.83.63.50</ip>
      <website>http://www.sfyh.com/totes-snow-boots_ss</website>
      <content>This article gives the light in which we can observe the reality. This is very nice one and gives in-depth information</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="41081ec4-4155-48ab-bcfc-1292f3b86e16" approved="True">
      <date>2011-02-17 08:50:56</date>
      <author>carrera sunglass</author>
      <email>hang@126.com</email>
      <ip>216.83.63.50</ip>
      <website>http://www.sfyh.com/Carrera-sunglass_4962_38763_prod.html</website>
      <content>Nice to be visiting your blog again, it has been months for me. Well this article that i've been waited for so long. I need this article to complete my assignment in the college, and it has same topic with your article. Thanks, great share. </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="c17ce343-8a1e-4d30-b27a-4b22e0b177b0" approved="True">
      <date>2011-02-25 05:26:33</date>
      <author>led flashlights</author>
      <email>hang@126.com</email>
      <ip>216.83.63.50</ip>
      <website>http://www.sfyh.com/led-flashlights_ss</website>
      <content>Excellent read, I just passed this onto a colleague who was doing a little research on that. And he actually bought me lunch because I found it for him smile So let me rephrase that: Thanks for lunch!
</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="83caa2cd-af7c-47ae-8c5b-b90e23c21f43" approved="True">
      <date>2011-02-28 08:49:12</date>
      <author>cheap wow gold</author>
      <email>goldswow.com@baidu.cn</email>
      <ip>58.20.69.90</ip>
      <website>http://www.goldswow.com/</website>
      <content>Hi I reach your site by mistake when i was searching bing for this wii issue cheap wow gold, I must&amp;amp;amp;nbsp;say your site is really helpful I also love the design, its amazing!. I dont have that much time to read all your post at the moment&amp;amp;amp;nbsp;but I have bookmarked your site&amp;amp;amp;nbsp;and also signed up for your RSS feeds. I will be back in a day or two. thanks for a great site.Hi I reach your site by mistake when i was searching bing for this wii issue wow items, I must&amp;amp;amp;nbsp;say your site is really helpful I also love the design, its amazing!. I dont have that much time to read all your post at the moment&amp;amp;amp;nbsp;but I have bookmarked your site&amp;amp;amp;nbsp;and also signed up for your RSS feeds. I will be back in a day or two. thanks for a great site.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="190e3603-30a0-4c82-b759-33f1dded2be2" approved="True">
      <date>2011-02-28 11:57:27</date>
      <author>cheap wow gold</author>
      <email>goldswow.com@baidu.cn</email>
      <ip>119.39.85.44</ip>
      <website>http://www.goldswow.com/</website>
      <content>The Zune concentrates on being a Portable Media Player. Not a web browser. Not a game machine. Maybe in the future it'll do even better in those areas cheap wow gold, but for now it's a fantastic way to organize and listen to your music and videos, and is without peer in that regard. The iPod's strengths are its web browsing and apps. If those sound more compelling, perhaps it is your best choice.The Zune concentrates on being a Portable Media Player. Not a web browser. Not a game machine. Maybe in the future it'll do even better in those areas wow items, but for now it's a fantastic way to organize and listen to your music and videos, and is without peer in that regard. The iPod's strengths are its web browsing and apps. If those sound more compelling, perhaps it is your best choice.</content>
    </comment>
  </comments>
  <categories>
    <category>0d8cc69b-489f-47b7-be20-41e36e530fc1</category>
    <category>914c30a5-7cad-46e9-b744-e7601e72da77</category>
  </categories>
  <notifications />
</post>