<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
  <author>Zasz</author>
  <title>Play DotA</title>
  <description>Warcraft 3 dota mod information</description>
  <content>&lt;div style="background-color: black"&gt;&lt;img src="/ThonHttpHandlers/Image.ashx?picturepath=~/App_Data/ZaszBlog/Files\E005.gif" alt="" /&gt;&lt;img src="/ThonHttpHandlers/Image.ashx?picturepath=~/App_Data/ZaszBlog/Files\H000.gif" alt="" /&gt;&lt;img src="/ThonHttpHandlers/Image.ashx?picturepath=~/App_Data/ZaszBlog/Files\Hdgo.gif" alt="" /&gt;&lt;img src="/ThonHttpHandlers/Image.ashx?picturepath=~/App_Data/ZaszBlog/Files\PotM.gif" alt="" /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;For those of you who want to experience the 5v5 Multiplayer excitement in DotA AllStars, You can use the G-Arena or Garena client, all you need is Warcraft 3 Frozen Throne, the latest dota map , and the latest dota AI map (from &lt;a href="http://www.getdota.com/" target="_blank" title="DotA"&gt;http://www.getdota.com/&lt;/a&gt;) , and the Garena Gaming client . With 2mbps Internet connection of course.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A standard game in Garena Dota India room takes about 4 - 14 mb traffic (based on time of gameplay), even the longest game is cant cross the 15 mb traffic and most&amp;#39;ll be over within 5 mb.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;	&lt;li&gt;Go to &lt;a href="http://www.garena.com/" target="_blank"&gt;www.garena.com&lt;/a&gt;	, Register as free member (choose a dota based username for the &amp;quot;cool&amp;quot;	factor) , download the client software, around 30 mb I think.&lt;/li&gt;	&lt;li&gt;Install the software , open it and enter in your username &amp;amp; password and login.TURN THE FIREWALL OFF (from control panel)&lt;/li&gt;	&lt;li&gt;Then click on India rooms join a level 1 room with atleast more than 100 people in it.. then click on start game button.&lt;/li&gt;	&lt;li&gt;It &amp;#39;ll ask for the path of the game executable.. browse to the folder where u copied warcraft 3 and choose FrozenThrone.exe&lt;/li&gt;	&lt;li&gt;In the game menu go to lan game . Wait till you see a game(mostly	no need to wait.. u can see 3 or 4 games at all times) and join a game..&lt;br /&gt;	call me if u have any problems&lt;/li&gt;	&lt;li&gt;U need to kno the jargon:&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;afk = away from keyboard&lt;br /&gt;bb = bye bye&lt;br /&gt;bbl = be back later&lt;br /&gt;brb = be right back&lt;br /&gt;bs = bullshit OR backstab (an ambush)&lt;br /&gt;buff = make something better (an ability, stats, items etc)&lt;br /&gt;dw = dont worry&lt;br /&gt;gj = good job&lt;br /&gt;gl hf = good luck, have fun&lt;br /&gt;gw = good work&lt;br /&gt;imba = imbalanced&lt;br /&gt;lo = hello&lt;br /&gt;lol = laughing out loud&lt;br /&gt;nerf = make something worse (an ability, stats, items etc)&lt;br /&gt;nm = nvm = never mind&lt;br /&gt;ppl = people&lt;br /&gt;gg = good game&lt;br /&gt;spikin = experiencing hangs every few seconds (spikes)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Shortforms&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;b = back = retreat&lt;br /&gt;bkb = black king bar&lt;br /&gt;dd = doubledamage&lt;br /&gt;dmg = damage&lt;br /&gt;dota = defence of the ancients&lt;br /&gt;dps = damage per second&lt;br /&gt;eos = eye of skadi&lt;br /&gt;fend = defend&lt;br /&gt;gg = good game&lt;br /&gt;ks = killsteal&lt;br /&gt;mkb = monkey king bar&lt;br /&gt;pub = pubbie = public = public game&lt;br /&gt;rax = barracks, if yours is destroyed the opposing team&amp;#39;s creeps get stronger &lt;br /&gt;regen = regeneration&lt;br /&gt;rm = remake&lt;br /&gt;ror = ring of regenation&lt;br /&gt;roh = ring of health&lt;br /&gt;ulti = a hero&amp;#39;s ultimate spell&lt;br /&gt;crit = critical&lt;br /&gt;HP = hit points&lt;br /&gt;MP = mana points&lt;br /&gt;noob = someone relatively new to the game&lt;br /&gt;XP = Experience&lt;br /&gt;AoE= Area of effect. Used to describe spells which target an area rather then a single unit&lt;br /&gt;dps = damage per second&lt;br /&gt;ff = forfeit&lt;br /&gt;mia = missing in action. Used to tell others that the enemy hero(s) in your lane is missing&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Item shortforms&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Harby/OD = Harbinger, the Obsidian Destroyer&lt;br /&gt;BM = Rexxar, the BeastMaster&lt;br /&gt;CM = Crystal Maiden&lt;br /&gt;Pig/BB = Rigwarl, BristleBack&lt;br /&gt;PA = Phantom Assassin&lt;br /&gt;clinkz = Bone Clinkz, the BoneFletcher&lt;br /&gt;sheepstick = Guinsoo&amp;#39;s Scythe of Vyse&lt;br /&gt;sk = Sand King, Soul Keeper, Skeleton King&lt;br /&gt;sniper = Kardel Sharpeye, the Dwarven Sniper&lt;br /&gt;blink dagger = Dagger of Escape&lt;br /&gt;BoT = Boots of Travel&lt;br /&gt;Deso = Stygian Desolator&lt;br /&gt;HoT = Heart of Tarrasque&lt;br /&gt;Necro = Necromonicon&lt;br /&gt;RoB = Ring of the Basilus&lt;br /&gt;Manta = Manta Style&lt;br /&gt;Null = Null talisman&lt;br /&gt;HoM/Midas = Hand of Midas&lt;br /&gt;Basher = Cranium Basher&lt;br /&gt;Mael = Maelstrom&lt;br /&gt;HoD = Helm of the Dominator&lt;br /&gt;BF/Bfury = Battlefury&lt;br /&gt;Divine = Divine Rapier&lt;br /&gt;Angha / Scepter = Anghamins Scepter&lt;br /&gt;MoM = Mask of Madness&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;font size="3"&gt;&lt;font color="red"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Game Modes&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;font size="3"&gt;&lt;font color="red"&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Typed by the blue player (usually the host) within the first 15 secondsof the game. As a general rule, the planned game mode(s) should alwaysbe included in the game name. Modes can now be entered on one line like&amp;quot;-apidsh&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;-dm -ar -sc&amp;quot;. You do not need to worry about the orderyou enter the modes in, the game will handle it or warn you (and giveyou another chance) if the mode is incorrect/incompatible.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;font color="skyblue"&gt;-ap / -allpick&lt;/font&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Player may pick hero from all teams&amp;#39; taverns.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;font color="skyblue"&gt;-ar / -allrandom&lt;/font&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;All players start off with a random hero chosen out of both taverns.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;font color="skyblue"&gt;-du / duplicate mode&lt;/font&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;More than one copy of the same hero may be selected by different players. Currently only compatible with -allrandom mode.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;font color="skyblue"&gt;-mm / -mirrormatch&lt;/font&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Players may choose a hero as normal, but after a given period of time,the teams will be randomized according to the heroes chosen by bothsides and corresponding players given the same hero. The resultingteams will be identical, hence the name of the mode (5v5 game = 5 pairsof heros chosen from 10 possible ones).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;font color="skyblue"&gt;-rd / -randomdraft&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This command gives a pool of 20(22?) heroes to pick in a 1-2-2-2-2-1format, with either blue or pink going first, and then it will workdown the rest of the colors with the team that is picking alternatingeach time. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;font color="skyblue"&gt;-sc / super creeps&lt;/font&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Random super creeps may spawn every creep wave. Completely randomexcept for the progression of supercreeps (Golems, Scary Fish, AncientHydra) and played for the increased gameplay dynamics. Not completelyconsidered &amp;quot;fair&amp;quot;, due to the randomness and inconsistency of the supercreeps spawning per side (e.g. Sentinels may receive spawns very latein the game compared to the Scourge getting spawns frequently earlieron).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;font color="skyblue"&gt;-em / easymode&lt;/font&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Building and tower hit points are reduced, higher rate of heroexperience and gold accumulation. This mode was previously known asshortmode (-sm).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;font color="skyblue"&gt;-dm / deathmatch&lt;/font&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If a player&amp;#39;s hero dies, that hero type is removed from gameplay andthe player chooses a new hero from the remaining selection. When a teamhas thirty deaths, it is defeated. (This mode is currently bugged inversion 6.12b when a hero dies he also loses 1 level)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;font color="skyblue"&gt;-id / itemdrop&lt;/font&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Enables random item drop upon death instead of losing money.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;font color="skyblue"&gt;-lm / leaguemode&lt;/font&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The teams will only be able to choose one hero at a time, until allplayers have picked their hero, in this order: Blue, Pink, Teal, LightBlue, Purple ... and finally Brown. This is to avoid one of the teamsonly choosing heroes countering the other teams heroes. This way thepicks are justly distributed.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;font color="skyblue"&gt;-teamrandom&lt;/font&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Players receive a random hero on his corresponding side (eitherSentinel or Scourge), he can repick for 500 gold during the firstminute of the game by using the command -repick (see below).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;font color="skyblue"&gt;-new&lt;/font&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Enables an additional tavern with a new hero at the bottom right of themap. It is to serve as a buffer for newly introduced heros which arenot yet balanced for normal play. Currently the only hero in thistavern is the Invoker. EDIT: This mode is no longer available.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;font color="skyblue"&gt;-as/ -aa/ -ai&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;All strength/ agility/ intelligence heroes mode. Only strength/ agility/ intelligence heroes can be picked.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;font color="skyblue"&gt;-sh / samehero&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;All players in the game will recieve the hero that the host either picks or randoms. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;font color="skyblue"&gt;-wtf&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;enables wtf mode. All spell cooldowns are removed, and heroes have limitless mana.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;font size="3"&gt;&lt;font color="red"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Commands available to all players&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;font color="skyblue"&gt;-repick&lt;/font&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Gives you a new, random hero if you&amp;#39;re in an -ar game and you want tochange your hero (costs 500 gold). There is a limited time window forrepicking (the maximum number of &amp;quot;repicks&amp;quot; is one).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;font color="skyblue"&gt;-refresh&lt;/font&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;With the Phantom Assassin (PA), it is used for refreshing her&amp;quot;invisibility&amp;quot; (due to a bug that removes this invisibility on death).Since the release of version 6.10, it no longer casts a Frost Novaanimation on the PA.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;font color="skyblue"&gt;-random&lt;/font&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Selects a random hero from your side. You can repick another randomhero by typing -repick, but it costs 150g. (note the different goldcosts for repicking in -allrandom games and repicking when you yourselfchoose to -random.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;font color="skyblue"&gt;-movespeed&lt;/font&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Displays current move speed (for debugging and informational purposes). Also works with -ms.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;font color="skyblue"&gt;-recreate&lt;/font&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For heroes that have the ability to undergo a metamorphosis that is nottied to the unit in the world editor map, namely Dragon Knight,Lycanthropy, Lifestealer, and Soul Keeper, where there are occasionalproblems with losing control of the unit. This is resolved by bringingthe unit back to the &amp;#39;fountain&amp;#39; area and typing this command. Thecommand has a 200 second channeling time, to prevent abuses.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;font color="skyblue"&gt;-unstuck&lt;/font&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Transports your hero to the fountain after 50 seconds; it&amp;#39;s used whenyou are stuck in a unmovable place (e.g. trapped in an area of trees).You cannot move while transporting.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;font color="skyblue"&gt;-matchup&lt;/font&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Displays the enemy players&amp;#39; alias along with which hero they are currently controlling. Also works with -ma.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;font color="skyblue"&gt;-cs/-cson/off&lt;/font&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Shows you your current creep kills. The board(cson) continually shows the number, while the normal command does not.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;font color="skyblue"&gt;-swaphero&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Allows you to select any teammate from a menu. That teammate will begiven the option to either select &amp;#39;yes&amp;#39; or &amp;#39;no&amp;#39; to the question if hewants to trade his hero with you. If he chooses &amp;#39;yes&amp;#39;, all items willbe carried over and control over the hero switches. If he chooses &amp;#39;no&amp;#39;,nothing will happen. Either way, you cannot use the command -swapheroagain. Each player may use this command once, so it is possible thatone hero is swapped between multiple players. This command cannot betyped after the first wave of creep commences.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;font color="skyblue"&gt;-disablehelp / -enablehelp&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;These two commands are designed to prevent abuses of Chen&amp;#39;s Test ofFaith. If you type -disablehelp at the beginning of the game, Chen&amp;#39;sTest of Faith will not work on you. If you type -enablehelp later on,Chen&amp;#39;s spell will work on you.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;font color="skyblue"&gt;-denyinfo&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This command shows the -cs board, and it also shows a ! whenever a creep or tower is denied. aka -di&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Refer to this thread: &lt;a href="http://www.dotaportal.com/forums/What-command-can-I-type-in-Dota-games-Complete-t11253.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.dotaportal.com/forums/What-comm...ete-t11253.html&lt;/a&gt; for a more comprehensive list of updated commands&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;font size="3"&gt;&lt;font color="red"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Heros&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;Heroes in Allstars are given certain classifications which willinfluence their method of play. For example, stunners (heroes which canstun enemies) are usually accompanied by assassins or nukers toefficiently kill an enemy hero.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;font color="skyblue"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Assassins&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Heroes which specialize at killing other heroes quickly throughphysical damage. All of them have some form of invisibility orambushing suddenly. Any hero with windwalk, an invisibility skill, orblink can fall into this category.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;font color="skyblue"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Disablers&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Heroes who possess the ability to disable other characters, basicallyforcing them into a disadvantage while they attempt to fight or flee.Disables include any spells that move the enemy without his or herconsent, stun an enemy, reduce movement speed, disallow movement,reduce damage, reduce attack speed, reduce armor, prevent physicalattack, or prevent spell-casting. Though many spells fall under thesecategories, the general rule of an effective disable is a spell thatcan extend an enemy&amp;#39;s presence in combat against his or her will, whichtherefore only includes the first four of the listed effects. Also,passive abilities are often ignored as disables. Rhasta and Lion aretwo famous examples, both having two disable skills (Lion has impaleand voodoo, rhasta has shackles and voodoo).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;font color="skyblue"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Nukers&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Heroes who possess the ability to cause a significant amount of damagein a single instant via use of activated abilities in lieu of aphysical attack. E.g. Lion with Impale and Finger of Death, Slayer withDragon Slave and Light Strike Array+Laguna Blade.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;font color="skyblue"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Support&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Heroes whose skills are meant to directly aid the rest of the team.Heroes with healing or protective skills fall into this category.Pushers can also be counted as support, although sometimes they can beused individually instead of working together with the team.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;font color="skyblue"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Pushers&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Heroes which can quickly destroy enemy towers and creep generators dueto their ability to summon additional units or deal damage to an areaof enemy creeps. E.g. Prophet with Force of Nature, Warlock withInfernals, and Keeper of the Light with Illuminate and Ignus Fatuus.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;font color="skyblue"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Spammers&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Heroes who spam offensive spells repeatedly in an attempt to kill anenemy hero or disrupt the opponents&amp;#39; play. This frequently causes enemyheroes to go back to their Fountain of Health to heal, thereby wastingtime and causing the enemy hero to lose experience. E.g. Zeus withLightning Arc and Death Prophet with Carrion Swarm and Witchcraft. A&amp;quot;spammer&amp;quot; is typically just a specific kind of nuker.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;font color="skyblue"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Stunners&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Heroes who possess the ability to stun other characters. Certain heroeshave passive skills enabling their attacks to have a chance ofstunning. When such heroes are able to keep the enemy constantlystunned it is known informally as permastun. E.g. Lion with Impale,Leoric with Storm Bolt, and Sand King with Burrowstrike.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;font color="skyblue"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tankers&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Heroes who can absorb huge amounts of damage with either high health orarmor count. Typically used to destroy enemy towers. E.g. TreantProtector with Living Armor, Centaur Warchief with high base Strengthand Great Fortitude, and Morphling with Morph Strength.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;-- &lt;br /&gt;~ Game on! ~&lt;br /&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <ispublished>True</ispublished>
  <iscommentsenabled>True</iscommentsenabled>
  <pubDate>2009-01-24 12:30:00</pubDate>
  <lastModified>2009-05-16 19:43:44</lastModified>
  <raters>1</raters>
  <rating>5</rating>
  <slug>Play-DotA</slug>
  <tags>
    <tag>games</tag>
    <tag>welcome</tag>
    <tag>dota</tag>
  </tags>
  <comments>
    <comment id="83d897ba-9e23-4a50-980d-0388240144e6" approved="True">
      <date>2009-05-31 20:56:46</date>
      <author>Samson Mano</author>
      <email>saminnx@gmail.com</email>
      <ip>117.199.137.67</ip>
      <content>Nice one</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="85b7260d-6aa6-4f19-911e-0ec26278cb1d" approved="True">
      <date>2009-11-24 23:07:45</date>
      <author>faxless payday loans</author>
      <email>jhagar1@cox.net</email>
      <ip>79.116.136.36</ip>
      <website>http://www.usapaydayloan.net/</website>
      <content>Do you make money out of this blog? just curious</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="a1d7077d-7387-49e9-954c-36f2365d17bc" approved="True">
      <date>2010-06-25 11:56:18</date>
      <author>wow gold</author>
      <email>DamianeSt-Pierre@gamehehe.com</email>
      <ip>118.249.147.98</ip>
      <website>http://www.gamehehe.com/</website>
      <content>This is a really good read for me. Must agree that you are one of the coolest bloggers I ever saw. Thanks for posting this useful article.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="5d25fb25-1ec1-4155-b858-266e1062b8ff" approved="True">
      <date>2010-06-25 12:42:16</date>
      <author>wow gold</author>
      <email>ClaudeRiel@wowgold365.com</email>
      <ip>58.20.49.124</ip>
      <website>http://www.wowgold365.com/</website>
      <content>Just wanted to give you a shout from the valley of the sun, great information. Much appreciated.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="837a4d0a-e9e3-4261-a5f1-07a4ef450f20" approved="True">
      <date>2010-06-25 13:51:37</date>
      <author>ff14 gil</author>
      <email>TempesteLemieux@ffxigil365.com/</email>
      <ip>58.20.49.124</ip>
      <website>http://www.ffxigil365.com/</website>
      <content>I have been looking towards looking at this process as well. Perfect read.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="f3c4ded7-e2fe-433e-9d1c-b475f17bfc61" approved="True">
      <date>2010-06-25 14:20:30</date>
      <author>Buy Wow Gold</author>
      <email>PierpontGalarneau@wowgold365.co.uk</email>
      <ip>58.20.49.124</ip>
      <website>http://www.ff14gilsaler.com/</website>
      <content>Im not going to say what everyone else has already said, but I do want to comment on your knowledge of the topic.  Youre truly well-informed.  I cant believe how much of this I just wasnt aware of.  Thank you for bringing more information to this topic for me.  Im truly grateful and really impressed.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="32e664d3-4697-4ba4-adf0-8f8de5714cfc" approved="True">
      <date>2010-06-26 13:55:05</date>
      <author>wow gold</author>
      <email>AlgernonGenereux@wowgold365.fr</email>
      <ip>58.20.49.124</ip>
      <website>http://www.wowgold365.fr/</website>
      <content>I was very pleased to find this site.I wanted to thank you for this great read!! I definitely enjoying every little bit of it and I have you bookmarked to check out new stuff you post.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="ad9c5168-4334-4501-985a-3e33e2168655" approved="True">
      <date>2010-06-26 14:05:02</date>
      <author>wow gold</author>
      <email>BlanchefleGrimard@gamesgoldsale.com</email>
      <ip>58.20.49.124</ip>
      <website>http://www.gamesgoldsale.com/</website>
      <content>Zune and iPod: Most people compare the Zune to the Touch, but after seeing how slim and surprisingly small and light it is, I consider it to be a rather unique hybrid that combines qualities of both the Touch and the Nano. It's very colorful and lovely OLED screen is slightly smaller than the touch screen, but the player itself feels quite a bit smaller and lighter. It weighs about 2/3 as much, and is noticeably smaller in width and height, while being just a hair thicker.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="781d8463-cffa-47b4-98e8-af88b81fc423" approved="True">
      <date>2010-06-26 15:21:08</date>
      <author>ff14 gil</author>
      <email>AubreyLereau@ff14gilsaler.com/</email>
      <ip>58.20.49.124</ip>
      <website>http://www.ff14gilsaler.com/</website>
      <content>One has to think through it before coming to a conclusion on about it,beautiful site I like the header.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="0cbfe7e8-0d3c-453c-919b-e9ac476abc43" approved="True">
      <date>2010-06-26 15:46:05</date>
      <author>wowgold</author>
      <email>LeoSellheim@visongold.com</email>
      <ip>58.20.49.124</ip>
      <website>http://www.goldteamsale.com/</website>
      <content>Hi! I was surfing and found your blog post?- nice! I love your blog.  Cheers! Melissa. G.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="8b96c686-4d6e-4ac7-b5d4-c83bb6a9cdef" approved="True">
      <date>2010-06-28 07:22:50</date>
      <author>wow gold</author>
      <email>IvenBonneville@gmail.com</email>
      <ip>58.20.49.124</ip>
      <website>http://www.wowgold365.co.uk/</website>
      <content>was very pleased to find this site.I wanted to thank you for this great read!! I definitely enjoying every little bit of it and I have you bookmarked to check out new stuff you post.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="7f131fba-ea94-49c7-9743-f6451389efbe" approved="True">
      <date>2010-06-28 07:33:39</date>
      <author>wow gold</author>
      <email>DenisMigneault@wowgold365.de</email>
      <ip>58.20.49.124</ip>
      <website>http://www.wowgold365.de/</website>
      <content>unrefined raw sugar is not stripped of nutrients and trace minerals.. honey we all know has nutrients.. and if you havent heard of active honey i suggest researching it and find out the benefits it has.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="3fccb2b2-7955-472c-ba3a-30704de0cfe4" approved="True">
      <date>2010-06-28 08:55:52</date>
      <author>wow gold</author>
      <email>GemmaMaurice@wowgold-com.com/</email>
      <ip>58.20.49.124</ip>
      <website>http://www.wowgold-com.com/</website>
      <content>Hey, I am checking this site from my phone and it looks kinda trendy. Thought you?��d want to know. It?��s a great post though, didn?��t mess that up</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="16b45305-9eeb-4cb3-8aa1-7a26e3af9793" approved="True">
      <date>2010-06-28 09:18:55</date>
      <author>sell wow gold</author>
      <email>XavierreGirard@visongold.com</email>
      <ip>58.20.49.124</ip>
      <website>http://www.ff14gilsaler.com/</website>
      <content>Many thanks for this article. I looked for that on google and i find your blog.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="f191a2a1-bdd5-4975-81b3-add7a5e8b060" approved="True">
      <date>2010-06-29 10:02:15</date>
      <author>wow gold</author>
      <email>DielleCamus@wowgoldsale.fr</email>
      <ip>58.20.49.124</ip>
      <website>http://www.wowgoldsale.fr/</website>
      <content>This is a good post, but I was wondering how do I suscribe to the RSS feed?</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="2d477712-8f40-4d03-9c29-85c23bf8a1c3" approved="True">
      <date>2010-06-29 10:32:46</date>
      <author>wow gold</author>
      <email>OdeletteRaymond@gamehehe.fr</email>
      <ip>58.20.49.124</ip>
      <website>http://www.gamehehe.fr/</website>
      <content>Thanks for writing great info regarding the topic. I am a fan of your blog. Keep up the great job.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="c21c4507-c52a-4127-9362-2d5d99a7c4e8" approved="True">
      <date>2010-06-30 06:41:11</date>
      <author>wow gold</author>
      <email>IgnacePirouet@visongold.com</email>
      <ip>58.20.49.124</ip>
      <website>http://www.visongold.com/</website>
      <content>I admire the valuable information you offer in your articles. I will bookmark your blog and have my children check up here often. I am quite sure they will learn lots of new stuff here than anybody else!</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="649a510d-c81c-476f-826a-fccb7c973326" approved="True">
      <date>2010-06-30 06:51:02</date>
      <author>wow gold news</author>
      <email>LillyEHodgson@visongold.com</email>
      <ip>58.20.49.124</ip>
      <website>http://www.bye-wowgold.com/</website>
      <content>This article gives the light in which we can observe the reality. this is very nice one and gives indepth information. thanks for this nice article</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="e413e2b2-0108-47ad-a021-064094398a64" approved="True">
      <date>2010-08-04 13:28:33</date>
      <author>Timberland boots</author>
      <email>373751851@qq.com</email>
      <ip>59.58.175.242</ip>
      <website>http://www.timberlandshoesonline.com/</website>
      <content>I had just finished reading your articles，and this is very good! timberland boots uk Being a comprehensive trade solution provider offering sale services with free shipping to international buyers who are interested in shopping online.The products here are timberland boots outlet, timberland roll top boots and men timberland boots. As an online business platform mainly retailing, waterproof boots we provide our buyers with an efficient and manageable procurement process covering every phase of the international supply chain and streamlining trade channels. Also welcome wholesaling, feedback now!</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="e8feb2ad-7e53-40ac-af02-2413957d9314" approved="True">
      <date>2010-08-19 19:21:31</date>
      <author>wow gold</author>
      <email>GranvilleTherriault@goldteamsale.com</email>
      <ip>58.20.49.124</ip>
      <website>http://www.visongold.com/</website>
      <content>Very interesting topic will bookmark your site to check if you write more about in the future.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="b91a15b7-fd6b-45b8-9ed4-c69984079fbd" approved="True">
      <date>2010-08-19 20:29:44</date>
      <author>randyrun</author>
      <email>BartlettCharlebois@wowgold365.co.uk</email>
      <ip>58.20.49.124</ip>
      <website>http://www.randyrungold.com/</website>
      <content>article marketing is a strong method that you should always include in your internet marketing arsenal. with article marketing you can bring visitors to your website at no cost. no need to worry about costly advertisement when you have article marketing.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="20048b1c-2416-4c1e-a65b-aa21b325dbf7" approved="True">
      <date>2010-08-19 21:11:12</date>
      <author>micro bikini</author>
      <email>BriceAbril@goldteamsale.com/</email>
      <ip>58.20.49.124</ip>
      <website>http://www.microbikinisale.com/</website>
      <content>Wow, what a blog!  I mean, you just have so much guts to go ahead and tell it like it is.  Youre what blogging needs, an open minded superhero who isnt afraid to tell it like it is.  This is definitely something people need to be up on.  Good luck in the future, man.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="a72dc8a2-32c6-4200-8ec4-08f1befc6916" approved="True">
      <date>2010-08-20 22:36:26</date>
      <author>ffxiv gil</author>
      <email>AlexisBarrientos@wowgold365.co.uk</email>
      <ip>58.20.49.124</ip>
      <website>http://www.buy-ffxiv-gils.com/</website>
      <content>I think i will add it in my favorite.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="97401275-9a39-426f-bc1c-fdc8dc45497f" approved="True">
      <date>2010-08-20 23:03:59</date>
      <author>wow items</author>
      <email>PhillipaLemelin@ff14gilsaler.com/</email>
      <ip>58.20.49.124</ip>
      <website>http://www.item4wow.com/</website>
      <content>Elegant bed. Its floating design is unique.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="16d6fb70-0e8e-4b7c-975b-58ae6ea6bfd8" approved="True">
      <date>2010-08-28 17:22:50</date>
      <author>game store</author>
      <email>AugusteTanguay@wowgold365.co.uk</email>
      <ip>58.20.49.124</ip>
      <website>http://www.karile.com/</website>
      <content>Sweet article and ideas. We share the same conclusions, at last I've found like minded people.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="e6727405-7b22-40ad-9668-cff16b0d8269" approved="True">
      <date>2010-08-28 19:12:15</date>
      <author>wow po</author>
      <email>MargauxLalonde@goldteamsale.com/</email>
      <ip>58.20.49.124</ip>
      <website>http://www.yokuar.com/</website>
      <content>Have you had problems with spammers?  I also use Blog Engine and I have some good anti-spam practices; please Email me if you are interested in an exchange of practices.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="ebcce0c8-966f-4c3d-b228-13b3ce15679c" approved="True">
      <date>2010-09-05 14:59:31</date>
      <author>latest game news</author>
      <email>GabrielQuiron@visongold.com</email>
      <ip>58.20.49.124</ip>
      <website>http://www.ohugame.com/</website>
      <content>Thank you for taking the time to chat about  this, I feel  fervently  about this and I enjoy learning about this subject.  If possible, as you gain data, please add to  this blog with new information.  I have found it really useful.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="9ae1c68f-74e3-4bf5-a9a0-959ed228f696" approved="True">
      <date>2010-09-05 15:56:19</date>
      <author>wow emblem</author>
      <email>LuceSouplet@cheap-ffxiv-gils.com/</email>
      <ip>58.20.49.124</ip>
      <website>http://www.wow-emblem.com/</website>
      <content>Found this accidently. Really nice read. Covers a lot of interest. I am planning to put my thoughts down in a blog like this, I just haven't done it yet.future posts</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="e7bb2f16-23dd-49e2-8fd1-b7cd3dda7339" approved="True">
      <date>2010-09-08 20:54:09</date>
      <author>IGE</author>
      <email>JamalZahirKhouri@wowgold365.co.uk</email>
      <ip>58.20.49.124</ip>
      <website>http://www.ige-2010.com/</website>
      <content>Very good post. Will you please write additional about this topic.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="6ede4b60-08c3-4f5b-8b61-2eb2ceedd551" approved="True">
      <date>2010-09-08 22:01:03</date>
      <author>wow gold EU</author>
      <email>BurkettMeilleur@ffxigilnet.com/</email>
      <ip>58.20.49.124</ip>
      <website>http://www.warlor.com/</website>
      <content>Keep working ,great job!</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="0a206279-bd1d-46f9-b82a-b21af343ff6e" approved="True">
      <date>2010-09-20 11:18:54</date>
      <author>Breitling Emergency Watches</author>
      <email>jfosi@hotmail.com</email>
      <ip>222.79.19.187</ip>
      <website>http://www.replica-watches-all.com/Replica-professional-collection-emergency_c2370</website>
      <content>towardward [url=http://www.replicawatchessuper.com/Replica-Blancpain-Collection-Blancpain-Women-Chronographe-Flyback---Rattrapante-3485F-1130-97B-Watch-women_l483]Blancpain Women Chronographe Flyback &amp;#224; Rattrapante[/url], you cylsecretder identify titanic asas a resultrtment of [url=http://www.replicawatchessuper.com/Replica-chopard-your-hour-watches_v196]Chopard Your Hour watches[/url] alby top ofg by [url=http://www.replica-watches-net.com/Replica-burberry-watches_g1679]Replica Burberry Watches[/url] which are assist architect commodities for ladies among men. our [url=http://www.buyhangbag.com/Hermes-Kelly-32cm-Togo-Leather-Gold-Gold-Hardware-Hardware-HandB-amsNJ32lan_n1379]Hermes Kelly 32cm Togo Leather Gold Gold Hardware Hardware HandB[/url] tolerate mimic Hermes, Chanel, Gucci, Burberry, Prada, Miu Miu as well Louis Vuitton hfurthermorebags after that so on. these [url=http://www.replica-watches-net.com/Replica-sp44_g1462]BRM Watches SP44[/url] are stunning compatible with the original[url=http://www.goshoppingnet.com]Pocket Watches[/url]. rider you are infinitely receptive in the [url=http://www.replica-watches-net.com/replica-cartier-montres-santos-de-cartier-santos-100-ref-w20106x8-unisex-watch_n5558]Cartier Montres Santos de Cartier - Santos 100 ref.: W20106X8 Unisex Watch[/url] and [url=http://www.buyhangbag.com/Replica-hermes_g46]Replica Hermes handbags[/url], no more than consolidate in [url=http://www.goshoppingnet.com/Sell-jaegerlecoultre-reverso-squadra-watches_c182]Jaeger-LeCoultre Reverso Squadra Watches[/url] on 4687812345118</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="ccb4024e-4d44-4c26-a082-d2846c4d72f5" approved="True">
      <date>2010-10-05 05:54:31</date>
      <author>ffxiv gil</author>
      <email>HarrisonMyer@wowgold-europe.com</email>
      <ip>118.250.69.149</ip>
      <website>http://www.ffxivgil365.com/</website>
      <content>Just thought i would comment and say neat theme. Just bought the Microwave. Its the best microwave I have ever had.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="dbc5ee81-013a-44c3-83f2-f536389dd4cd" approved="True">
      <date>2010-10-05 11:32:21</date>
      <author>world of warcraft gold</author>
      <email>CelineLebel@wowgold365.co.uk</email>
      <ip>118.250.69.149</ip>
      <website>http://www.cslgold.com/</website>
      <content>I completely agree with the above comment, the internet is with a doubt growing into the most important medium of communication across the globe and its due to sites like this that ideas are spreading so quickly.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="693aba0f-c456-4b8e-abc5-728712f1fdfb" approved="True">
      <date>2010-10-05 17:22:13</date>
      <author>buy cheap wow gold</author>
      <email>TaylaShore@wowgold-europe.com/</email>
      <ip>118.250.69.149</ip>
      <website>http://www.you-cataclysm.com/</website>
      <content>If you're still on the fence: grab your favorite earphones, head down to a Best Buy and ask to plug them into a Zune then an iPod and see which one sounds better to you, and which interface makes you smile more. Then you'll know which is right for you.</content>
    </comment>
  </comments>
  <categories>
    <category>bddabd05-73ba-4a63-a6c5-f97b5edea0fd</category>
    <category>0d8cc69b-489f-47b7-be20-41e36e530fc1</category>
  </categories>
  <notifications />
</post>